

3138 BATANGAS STREET HENSONVILLE SUBD.
ANGELES CITY, PH 2009
(+63) 926-193-3890
nunagdexter@gmail.com

BIOGRAPHY

I'm 23 years old web developer. I have almost 2 years of work experience in web development mainly using Javascript frameworks. I love to create websites and web applications, paying close attention to all the small details. Also I love to travel, workout and play basketball.

EXPERIENCE

FULLSTACK HQ, INC., ANGELES CITY, PAMPANGA — WEB DEVELOPER

SEPTEMBER 2017 - PRESENT

- Web Applications
 - MEAN Stack
 - MERN Stack
- Mobile Applications
 - o Ionic 3
- Others
 - Data scrape using nodejs
 - Admin panel using php

UPWORK / FREELANCER, ANGELES CITY, PAMPANGA — FREELANCE WEB DEV

NOVEMBER 2016 - PRESENT

- Online Market Place (MERN stack)
- Document Tracker (Angular 1.x, Bootstrap 3)
- SSL Certificate application and fixes
- Import/Export data using scripts (JavaScript, PHP, Bash)
- Wordpress small fixes (CSS3 or JavaScript)

RAIN WEB SOLUTIONS, ANGELES CITY, PAMPANGA — FRONTEND DEV TRAINEE

MAY 2016

Created a single page template (Bootstrap 3, CSS3, JavaScript)

EDUCATION

HOLY ANGEL UNIVERSITY, ANGELES CITY, PAMPANGA — BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

JUNE 2012 - NOVEMBER 2017, ANGELES CITY, PAMPANGA

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, BEM, JavaScript, PHP, Ionic, Angular, React, Nodejs, Expressjs, Gulp, SQLite, MySQL, MongoDB, Firebase

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Able to work under pressure, Flexible, Team player, Critical thinker